Annie?
Rachel!
Long time no see! How are you?
I'm great.
What a lovely surprise!
Great to see you!
Yeah! You too.
When did we last see each other?
Oh, I think it was about...
six years ago!
So ... where are you living these days?
Oh, not far from here...
I live on Hampton Street...
Do you know it?
Yes, I do. That's really close to the centre.
Mmm. How about you?
We live on Compton Road.
Oh - how nice!
My name's Mark, by the way.
Hi. Nice to meet you.
Nice to meet you, too.
Sorry, yes - Mark's my husband!
Husband - wow!
That's fantastic news.
When did you get married?
-Six months ago.
-Eight months ago.
It was six, Mark.
Well, congratulations!
I want to know all the details!
Look - I'm going to the café down the street now...
...to meet Leo, my boyfriend.
Would you both like to come?
Yeah, that sounds good.
Brilliant!
Let's go.